<theme>
    <variables>
        <systemName>3DO</systemName>
        <systemDescription>The 3DO Interactive Multiplayer is a 32-bit console originally launched by Panasonic in 1993, based on specifications by The 3DO Company. Designed by Dave Needle and RJ Mical, it was a high-end multimedia platform that also saw versions from Sanyo and Goldstar. Despite its advanced hardware for the time, its high launch price led to its discontinuation in 1996.</systemDescription>
        <systemManufacturer>Panasonic</systemManufacturer>
        <systemReleaseYear>1993</systemReleaseYear>
        <systemReleaseDate>1993-10-04</systemReleaseDate>
        <systemReleaseDateFormated>October 4, 1993</systemReleaseDateFormated>
        <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
        <systemCoverSize>752-1440</systemCoverSize>
        <systemCoverSizeType>portrait</systemCoverSizeType>
        <systemColor>d4a53a</systemColor>
        <systemColorPalette1>FF0000</systemColorPalette1>
        <systemColorPalette2>0000A0</systemColorPalette2>
        <systemColorPalette3>FFE41B</systemColorPalette3>
        <systemColorPalette4>23B14D</systemColorPalette4>
        <systemCartSize>1-1</systemCartSize>
    </variables>
    <language name="ar_SA">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>جهاز 3DO التفاعلي هو وحدة تحكم ألعاب 32 بت أطلقتها باناسونيك في عام 1993 بناءً على مواصفات شركة 3DO. تم تصميم النظام بواسطة ديف نيدل وآر جيه ميكال كمنصة وسائط متعددة متطورة، وصدرت منه نسخ لاحقاً من سانيو وغولد ستار. على الرغم من أجهزته القوية، أدى سعره المرتفع إلى إيقافه في عام 1996.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>وحدة التحكم</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="bs_BA">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>3DO Interactive Multiplayer je 32-bitna konzola koju je Panasonic lansirao 1993. godine prema specifikacijama kompanije 3DO. Dizajnirali su je Dave Needle i RJ Mical kao naprednu multimedijalnu platformu, a verzije su izdali i Sanyo i Goldstar. Uprkos snažnom hardveru, visoka cijena dovela je do prekida proizvodnje 1996. godine.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Konzola</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ca_ES">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>La 3DO Interactive Multiplayer és una consola de 32 bits llançada originalment per Panasonic el 1993 segons les especificacions de The 3DO Company. Dissenyada per Dave Needle i RJ Mical, va ser una plataforma multimèdia avançada amb versions de Sanyo i Goldstar. Tot i la seva potència, el seu elevat preu va provocar que es deixés de fabricar el 1996.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="de_DE">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Der 3DO Interactive Multiplayer ist eine 32-Bit-Konsole, die 1993 von Panasonic nach Spezifikationen der 3DO Company veröffentlicht wurde. Von Dave Needle und RJ Mical als High-End-Multimedia-Plattform entworfen, erschien sie auch in Versionen von Sanyo und Goldstar. Trotz starker Technik führte der hohe Preis 1996 zur Einstellung des Systems.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Konsole</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="es_ES">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>La 3DO Interactive Multiplayer es una consola de 32 bits lanzada originalmente por Panasonic en 1993, basada en las especificaciones de The 3DO Company. Diseñada por Dave Needle y RJ Mical, fue una plataforma multimedia avanzada que contó con versiones de Sanyo y Goldstar. A pesar de su potencia, su elevado precio de mercado limitó su éxito hasta su cese en 1996.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="fr_FR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>La 3DO Interactive Multiplayer est une console 32 bits lancée par Panasonic en 1993 selon les spécifications de The 3DO Company. Conçue par Dave Needle et RJ Mical comme une plateforme multimédia haut de gamme, elle a aussi été produite par Sanyo et Goldstar. Malgré ses performances, son prix élevé a conduit à l'arrêt de sa production en 1996.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="hr_HR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>3DO Interactive Multiplayer je 32-bitna konzola koju je Panasonic lansirao 1993. godine prema specifikacijama tvrtke 3DO. Dizajnirali su je Dave Needle i RJ Mical kao naprednu multimedijsku platformu, a verzije su izdali i Sanyo i Goldstar. Unatoč snažnom hardveru, visoka cijena dovela je do prekida proizvodnje 1996. godine.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Konzola</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="it_IT">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Il 3DO Interactive Multiplayer è una console a 32 bit lanciata da Panasonic nel 1993 su specifiche della 3DO Company. Progettata da Dave Needle e RJ Mical come piattaforma multimediale d'avanguardia, fu prodotta anche da Sanyo e Goldstar. Nonostante l'hardware evoluto, l'alto prezzo di lancio ne decretò la fine nel 1996.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ja_JP">
         Japanese
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>3DOインタラクティブ・マルチプレイヤーは、3DO社の仕様に基づき1993年にパナソニックから発売された32bitゲーム機です。デイブ・ニードルとRJ・ミカルによって設計された高性能なマルチメディア機で、三洋電機やゴールドスターからも発売されました。しかし、高価格がネックとなり1996年に生産終了となりました。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>コンソール</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ko_KR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>3DO 인터랙티브 멀티플레이어는 3DO 컴퍼니의 규격에 따라 1993년 파나소닉이 출시한 32비트 콘솔입니다. 데이브 니들과 RJ 마이클이 설계한 고성능 멀티미디어 플랫폼으로 산요와 골드스타에서도 출시되었습니다. 뛰어난 성능에도 불구하고 높은 출시 가격으로 인해 1996년 단종되었습니다.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>콘솔</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="nl_NL">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>De 3DO Interactive Multiplayer is een 32-bits console die in 1993 door Panasonic werd uitgebracht op basis van specificaties van The 3DO Company. Ontworpen door Dave Needle en RJ Mical als een geavanceerd multimediaplatform, verschenen er ook versies van Sanyo en Goldstar. Ondanks de sterke hardware leidde de hoge prijs in 1996 tot de stopzetting.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="pl_PL">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>3DO Interactive Multiplayer to 32-bitowa konsola wydana przez Panasonic w 1993 roku na podstawie specyfikacji The 3DO Company. Zaprojektowana przez Dave'a Needle'a i RJ Micala jako zaawansowana platforma multimedialna, doczekała się wersji od Sanyo i Goldstar. Pomimo potężnej specyfikacji, wysoka cena doprowadziła do zakończenia produkcji w 1996 roku.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Konsola</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="pt_BR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>O 3DO Interactive Multiplayer é um console de 32 bits lançado pela Panasonic em 1993, baseado nas especificações da The 3DO Company. Projetado por Dave Needle e RJ Mical como uma plataforma multimídia de ponta, também teve versões da Sanyo e Goldstar. Apesar do hardware avançado, seu alto preço de lançamento causou sua descontinuação em 1996.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="pt_PT">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>A 3DO Interactive Multiplayer é uma consola de 32 bits lançada pela Panasonic em 1993, baseada nas especificações da The 3DO Company. Projetada por Dave Needle e RJ Mical como uma plataforma multimédia avançada, também teve versões da Sanyo e Goldstar. Apesar do hardware potente, o seu elevado preço levou à interrupção da produção em 1996.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ro_RO">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>3DO Interactive Multiplayer este o consolă pe 32 de biți lansată de Panasonic în 1993, bazată pe specificațiile The 3DO Company. Proiectată de Dave Needle și RJ Mical ca o platformă multimedia de înaltă performanță, a avut versiuni și de la Sanyo și Goldstar. În ciuda hardware-ului avansat, prețul ridicat a dus la oprirea producției în 1996.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Consolă</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ru_RU">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>3DO Interactive Multiplayer — это 32-битная консоль, выпущенная Panasonic в 1993 году по спецификациям The 3DO Company. Разработанная Дейвом Нидлом и Джеем Микалом как передовая мультимедийная платформа, она также выпускалась Sanyo и Goldstar. Несмотря на мощное железо, высокая цена привела к прекращению производства в 1996 году.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Консоль</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="sr_RS">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>3DO Interactive Multiplayer je 32-bitna konzola koju je Panasonic lansirao 1993. godine prema specifikacijama kompanije 3DO. Dizajnirali su je Dave Needle i RJ Mical kao naprednu multimedijalnu platformu, a verzije su izdali i Sanyo i Goldstar. Uprkos snažnom hardveru, visoka cena dovela je do prekida proizvodnje 1996. godine.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Конзола</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="sv_SE">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>3DO Interactive Multiplayer är en 32-bitars konsol som lanserades av Panasonic 1993 baserat på specifikationer från The 3DO Company. Den designades av Dave Needle och RJ Mical som en avancerad multimediaplattform och släpptes även av Sanyo och Goldstar. Trots kraftfull hårdvara ledde det höga priset till att den lades ner 1996.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Konsol</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="zh_CN">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>3DO Interactive Multiplayer 是松下于 1993 年根据 3DO 公司的规格推出的 32 位游戏机。由 Dave Needle 和 RJ Mical 设计，定位为高端多媒体平台，三洋和金星也推出了相应版本。尽管硬件领先，但由于售价过高，该系统于 1996 年停产。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>游戏机</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="zh_TW">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>3DO Interactive Multiplayer 是 Panasonic 於 1993 年根據 3DO 公司的規格推出的 32 位元遊戲機。由 Dave Needle 和 RJ Mical 設計，定位為高端多媒體平台，三洋和金星也推出了相應版本。儘管硬體領先，但由於售價過高，該系統於 1996 年停產。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>遊戲機</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
</theme>