<theme>
    <variables>
        <systemName>FinalBurn Alpha</systemName>
        <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) is a source-available arcade emulator based on FinalBurn (2000). After FinalBurn stopped in 2001, its code spread widely and led to many unofficial builds—FBA became the most successful. It supports a huge range of systems, runs fast on modest hardware, and keeps a clean, simple interface.</systemDescription>
        <systemManufacturer>FBA Team</systemManufacturer>
        <systemReleaseYear>2000</systemReleaseYear>
        <systemReleaseDate>2000</systemReleaseDate>
        <systemReleaseDateFormated>2000</systemReleaseDateFormated>
        <systemHardwareType>Emulator</systemHardwareType>
        <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
        <systemCoverSizeType>portrait</systemCoverSizeType>
        <systemColor>5B60B7</systemColor>
        <systemColorPalette1>CF8A61</systemColorPalette1>
        <systemColorPalette2>FE7B07</systemColorPalette2>
        <systemColorPalette3>231F20</systemColorPalette3>
        <systemColorPalette4>FFFFFF</systemColorPalette4>
        <systemCartSize>1-1</systemCartSize>
    </variables>

    <language name="ar_SA">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) هو محاكي آركيد متاح المصدر يعتمد على FinalBurn (عام 2000). بعد توقف FinalBurn في 2001 انتشرت شفرته وظهرت نسخ غير رسمية عديدة، وكان FBA الأنجح بينها. يدعم أنظمة كثيرة جدًا، يعمل بسرعة على العتاد المتواضع، ويقدم واجهة واضحة وبسيطة.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>المحاكي</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="bs_BA">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) je arkadni emulator s dostupnim izvorom, zasnovan na FinalBurnu (2000). Nakon što je FinalBurn stao 2001., kod se široko proširio i nastale su mnoge neslužbene verzije — FBA je postao najuspješniji. Podržava ogroman broj sistema, radi brzo i na slabijem hardveru, i ima čist, jednostavan interfejs.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulator</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="ca_ES">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) és un emulador d’arcade amb codi disponible basat en FinalBurn (2000). Després que FinalBurn s’aturés el 2001, el seu codi es va difondre i van aparèixer moltes versions no oficials; FBA en va ser la més exitosa. Dona suport a molts sistemes, funciona ràpid en maquinari modest i ofereix una interfície clara i senzilla.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulator</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="de_DE">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) ist ein quelloffen verfügbares Arcade-Emulatorprojekt, das auf FinalBurn (2000) basiert. Nachdem FinalBurn 2001 eingestellt wurde, verbreitete sich der Code stark und führte zu vielen inoffiziellen Builds – FBA wurde davon der erfolgreichste. Es unterstützt sehr viele Systeme, läuft schnell auch auf schwächerer Hardware und bietet eine klare, einfache Oberfläche.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulator</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="es_ES">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) es un emulador arcade con código fuente disponible basado en FinalBurn (2000). Tras detenerse FinalBurn en 2001, su código se difundió ampliamente y surgieron muchas versiones no oficiales; FBA fue la más exitosa. Soporta una enorme cantidad de sistemas, rinde muy bien en hardware modesto y ofrece una interfaz clara y sencilla.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulador</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="fr_FR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) est un émulateur d’arcade dont le code est disponible, basé sur FinalBurn (2000). Après l’arrêt de FinalBurn en 2001, le code s’est largement diffusé et a donné naissance à de nombreuses versions non officielles — FBA est devenue la plus aboutie. Il supporte énormément de systèmes, tourne très bien sur du matériel modeste et propose une interface claire et simple.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulateur</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="hr_HR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) je arkadni emulator s dostupnim izvornim kodom, baziran na FinalBurnu (2000). Nakon što je FinalBurn zaustavljen 2001., kod se široko proširio i nastale su mnoge neslužbene verzije — FBA je postao najuspješniji. Podržava jako mnogo sustava, radi brzo i na skromnijem hardveru te nudi čisto i jednostavno sučelje.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulator</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="it_IT">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) è un emulatore arcade con sorgenti disponibili basato su FinalBurn (2000). Dopo l’arresto di FinalBurn nel 2001, il codice si è diffuso e ha portato a molte versioni non ufficiali — FBA è diventata la più riuscita. Supporta tantissimi sistemi, è veloce anche su hardware modesto e offre un’interfaccia pulita e semplice.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulatore</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="ja_JP">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha（FBA）は、FinalBurn（2000年）を元にしたソース公開のアーケードエミュレータです。FinalBurnが2001年に停止した後、コードが広く流通して多数の非公式版が生まれ、その中でもFBAが最も成功しました。対応システムが非常に多く、軽快に動作し、シンプルで分かりやすいUIが特徴です。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>エミュレータ</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="ko_KR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha(FBA)는 FinalBurn(2000)을 기반으로 한 소스 공개 아케이드 에뮬레이터입니다. FinalBurn이 2001년에 중단된 뒤 코드가 널리 퍼지며 다양한 비공식 버전이 생겼고, 그중 FBA가 가장 성공적이었습니다. 매우 많은 시스템을 지원하고, 사양이 낮은 기기에서도 빠르게 동작하며, 깔끔하고 단순한 UI를 제공합니다.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>에뮬레이터</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="nl_NL">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) is een arcade-emulator met beschikbare broncode, gebaseerd op FinalBurn (2000). Nadat FinalBurn in 2001 stopte, verspreidde de code zich breed en ontstonden er veel onofficiële builds—waarvan FBA de succesvolste werd. Het ondersteunt heel veel systemen, draait snel op bescheiden hardware en heeft een heldere, eenvoudige interface.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulator</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="pl_PL">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) to emulator arcade z dostępnym kodem źródłowym, oparty na FinalBurn (2000). Po zatrzymaniu FinalBurn w 2001 roku kod był szeroko rozpowszechniany i powstało wiele nieoficjalnych wersji — FBA okazał się najbardziej udany. Obsługuje ogromną liczbę systemów, działa szybko na skromnym sprzęcie i ma przejrzysty, prosty interfejs.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulator</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="pt_BR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) é um emulador de arcade com código-fonte disponível, baseado no FinalBurn (2000). Após o FinalBurn parar em 2001, o código se espalhou e surgiram muitas versões não oficiais — e o FBA foi a mais bem-sucedida. Ele suporta muitos sistemas, roda rápido em hardware modesto e oferece uma interface limpa e simples.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulador</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="pt_PT">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) é um emulador de arcade com código-fonte disponível, baseado no FinalBurn (2000). Depois de o FinalBurn parar em 2001, o código difundiu-se e surgiram muitas versões não oficiais — e o FBA foi a mais bem-sucedida. Suporta muitos sistemas, corre bem em hardware modesto e oferece uma interface limpa e simples.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulador</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="ro_RO">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) este un emulator arcade cu sursă disponibilă, bazat pe FinalBurn (2000). După ce FinalBurn s-a oprit în 2001, codul s-a răspândit pe scară largă și au apărut multe versiuni neoficiale — iar FBA a devenit cea mai reușită. Suportă foarte multe sisteme, rulează rapid pe hardware modest și are o interfață clară și simplă.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulator</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="ru_RU">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) — аркадный эмулятор с доступными исходниками, основанный на FinalBurn (2000). После остановки FinalBurn в 2001 году код широко распространился и появилось множество неофициальных сборок — наиболее успешной стала FBA. Он поддерживает огромное число систем, быстро работает даже на скромном железе и имеет понятный, простой интерфейс.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Эмулятор</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="sr_RS">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) је аркадни емулатор са доступним изворним кодом, заснован на FinalBurn-у (2000). Након што је FinalBurn заустављен 2001. године, код се широко проширио и настале су многе незваничне верзије — а FBA је постао најуспешнији. Подржава огроман број система, ради брзо и на скромнијем хардверу и има јасан, једноставан интерфејс.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Емулатор</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="sv_SE">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha (FBA) är en arkademulator med tillgänglig källkod, baserad på FinalBurn (2000). Efter att FinalBurn stoppade 2001 spreds koden brett och många inofficiella versioner uppstod — där FBA blev den mest framgångsrika. Den stöder väldigt många system, är snabb även på enklare hårdvara och har ett tydligt, enkelt gränssnitt.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulator</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="zh_CN">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha（FBA）是一款源代码可用的街机模拟器，基于 FinalBurn（2000）。FinalBurn 于 2001 年停止后，代码被广泛传播并出现许多非官方版本，其中 FBA 最为成功。它支持的系统非常多，在较低配置上也能快速运行，并提供清晰简单的界面。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>仿真器</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="zh_TW">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Alpha（FBA）是以 FinalBurn（2000）為基礎、可取得原始碼的街機模擬器。FinalBurn 於 2001 年停止後，程式碼廣泛流傳並衍生出許多非官方版本，其中 FBA 最為成功。它支援的系統非常多，在較低規格上也能快速運作，並提供清楚、簡單的介面。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>仿真器</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
</theme>
