<theme>
    <variables>
        <systemName>FinalBurn Neo</systemName>
        <systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo (FBNeo) is the latest and most active branch of the FinalBurn emulator series. It is a highly optimized multi-system emulator designed to provide high-accuracy emulation for arcade games and select home consoles. FBNeo supports a vast library of hardware, including Capcom CPS1/2/3, SNK Neo Geo, Sega System 16, and many other classic arcade systems, making it a cornerstone of modern retro-gaming.</systemDescription>
        <systemManufacturer>Various</systemManufacturer>
        <systemHardwareType>Arcade / Emulator</systemHardwareType>
        <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
        <systemCoverSizeType>portrait</systemCoverSizeType>
        <systemColor>e51a2e</systemColor>
        <systemColorPalette1>e51a2e</systemColorPalette1>
        <systemColorPalette2>ffffff</systemColorPalette2>
        <systemColorPalette3>222222</systemColorPalette3>
        <systemColorPalette4>999999</systemColorPalette4>
        <systemCartSize>1-1</systemCartSize>
    </variables>
    <language name="ar_SA"><variables><systemDescription>أحدث نسخة نشطة من سلسلة محاكيات FinalBurn، مصمم لمحاكاة ألعاب الأركيد بدقة عالية جداً.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="de_DE"><variables><systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo ist der aktuellste Zweig der FinalBurn-Serie, optimiert für präzise Arcade-Emulation von CPS bis Neo Geo.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="es_ES"><variables><systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo es la rama más activa de los emuladores FinalBurn, diseñada para emular recreativas y consolas clásicas. Destaca por su alta optimización y soporte para placas míticas como CPS y Neo Geo.</systemDescription><systemHardwareType>Arcade / Emulador</systemHardwareType></variables></language>
    <language name="fr_FR"><variables><systemDescription>FBNeo est la branche la plus active des émulateurs FinalBurn, offrant une grande précision pour les systèmes arcade et consoles.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="it_IT"><variables><systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo è l'ultimo ramo attivo della serie FinalBurn, focalizzato sull'emulazione accurata di arcade e console.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="ja_JP"><variables><systemDescription>アーケードゲームや各種家庭用ゲーム機を高度に再現する、FinalBurnシリーズの最新エミュレータです。</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="pl_PL"><variables><systemDescription>Najnowsza i najaktywniejsza gałąź emulatorów FinalBurn, zapewniająca wysoką precyzję emulacji automatów arcade.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="pt_BR"><variables><systemDescription>O FinalBurn Neo é o sucessor mais ativo da série FinalBurn, focado em emulação precisa de sistemas de arcade e consoles.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="ru_RU"><variables><systemDescription>Последняя активная ветка эмуляторов FinalBurn, обеспечивающая высокую точность работы аркадных систем и консолей.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="sv_SE"><variables><systemDescription>Den senaste aktiva grenen av FinalBurn-emulatorer, känd för hög noggrannhet vid arkademulering.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="zh_CN"><variables><systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo 是 FB 系列中最活跃的分支，致力于高精度模拟街机及部分家用机平台。</systemDescription></variables></language>
</theme>
