<theme>
    <variables>
        <systemName>FinalBurn Neo</systemName>
        <systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo is a multi-arcade emulator best known for running Neo Geo, Capcom, Konami, and Cave games. Developed by the FinalBurn team, it is an active fork of FinalBurn Alpha, maintained by former FBA developers after a licensing split.</systemDescription>
        <systemManufacturer>FBA Team</systemManufacturer>
        <systemReleaseYear>2002</systemReleaseYear>
        <systemReleaseDate>2002</systemReleaseDate>
        <systemReleaseDateFormated>2002</systemReleaseDateFormated>
        <systemHardwareType>Emulator</systemHardwareType>
        <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
        <systemCoverSizeType>portrait</systemCoverSizeType>
        <systemColor>5a64bb</systemColor>
        <systemColorPalette1>C0392B</systemColorPalette1>
        <systemColorPalette2>CF8A61</systemColorPalette2>
        <systemColorPalette3>231F20</systemColorPalette3>
        <systemColorPalette4>FFFFFF</systemColorPalette4>
        <systemCartSize>1-1</systemCartSize>
    </variables>

    <language name="es_ES">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo es un emulador multi-arcade conocido por ejecutar juegos de Neo Geo, Capcom, Konami y Cave. Está desarrollado por el equipo FinalBurn y es un fork activo de FinalBurn Alpha, mantenido tras una separación por licencias.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulador</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="fr_FR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo est un émulateur multi-arcade reconnu pour les jeux Neo Geo, Capcom, Konami et Cave. Développé par l’équipe FinalBurn, il s’agit d’un fork actif de FinalBurn Alpha issu d’une séparation liée aux licences.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulateur</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="de_DE">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo ist ein Multi-Arcade-Emulator für Neo Geo-, Capcom-, Konami- und Cave-Spiele. Er wird vom FinalBurn-Team entwickelt und ist ein aktiver Fork von FinalBurn Alpha nach einer Lizenztrennung.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulator</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="pt_BR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo é um emulador multi-arcade conhecido por rodar jogos de Neo Geo, Capcom, Konami e Cave. Desenvolvido pela equipe FinalBurn, é um fork ativo do FinalBurn Alpha após uma separação por licenças.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulador</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="it_IT">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo è un emulatore multi-arcade noto per i giochi Neo Geo, Capcom, Konami e Cave. Sviluppato dal team FinalBurn, è un fork attivo di FinalBurn Alpha nato dopo una separazione per licenze.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Emulatore</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="ja_JP">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Neoは、Neo Geo、Capcom、Konami、Caveのゲームで知られるマルチアーケードエミュレータです。FinalBurnチームにより開発され、FinalBurn Alphaから派生したアクティブなフォークです。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>エミュレータ</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

    <language name="zh_CN">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FinalBurn Neo 是一款多街机模拟器，以运行 Neo Geo、Capcom、Konami 和 Cave 游戏而闻名。由 FinalBurn 团队开发，是 FinalBurn Alpha 的一个活跃分支。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>仿真器</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>

</theme>
