<theme>
    <variables>
        <systemName>Famicom Disk System</systemName>
        <systemDescription>The Family Computer Disk System (FDS) was a peripheral for Nintendo's Famicom released in 1986. It used proprietary "Disk Cards" that provided more storage than contemporary cartridges, allowing for game saves and advanced soundtracks via an extra wavetable sound channel. It was the original platform for many iconic titles like Metroid, Kid Icarus, and The Legend of Zelda.</systemDescription>
        <systemManufacturer>Nintendo</systemManufacturer>
        <systemReleaseYear>1986</systemReleaseYear>
        <systemReleaseDate>1986-02-21</systemReleaseDate>
        <systemReleaseDateFormated>February 21, 1986</systemReleaseDateFormated>
        <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
        <systemCoverSize>1-1</systemCoverSize>
        <systemCoverSizeType>square</systemCoverSizeType>
        <systemColor>e30512</systemColor>
        <systemColorPalette1>e30512</systemColorPalette1>
        <systemColorPalette2>ffffff</systemColorPalette2>
        <systemColorPalette3>333333</systemColorPalette3>
        <systemColorPalette4>ffd700</systemColorPalette4>
        <systemCartSize>1-1</systemCartSize>
    </variables>
    <language name="ar_SA"><variables><systemDescription>ملحق لجهاز Famicom يستخدم أقراصاً مرنة قابلة لإعادة الكتابة، وكان المهد الأول لألعاب الأسطورة زيلدا ومترويد.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="de_DE"><variables><systemDescription>Das 1986 erschienene Famicom Disk System nutzte Disketten für größere Spiele und besseren Sound auf dem Nintendo Famicom.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="es_ES"><variables><systemDescription>Periférico para la Famicom lanzado en 1986 que utilizaba disquetes regrabables. Permitió juegos más extensos y con mejor sonido, siendo el hogar original de The Legend of Zelda y Metroid.</systemDescription><systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType></variables></language>
    <language name="fr_FR"><variables><systemDescription>Extension de la Famicom utilisant des disquettes réinscriptibles, offrant des capacités de sauvegarde et un son amélioré.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="it_IT"><variables><systemDescription>Periferica per il Famicom che utilizzava dischi magnetici, permettendo salvataggi e audio migliorato per titoli storici.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="ja_JP"><variables><systemDescription>1986年に発売されたファミコン用周辺機器。ディスクカードを採用し、ゼルダの伝説やメトロイドの初出ハードとなりました。</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="pl_PL"><variables><systemDescription>Urządzenie peryferyjne dla Famicoma wykorzystujące dyskietki, co pozwalało na zapis stanu gry i lepszą jakość dźwięku.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="pt_BR"><variables><systemDescription>Periférico do Famicom que usava disquetes regraváveis, permitindo jogos maiores e o salvamento de progresso.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="ru_RU"><variables><systemDescription>Периферийное устройство для Famicom, использовавшее дискеты для хранения игр, таких как первая Zelda и Metroid.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="sv_SE"><variables><systemDescription>Ett tillbehör till Famicom som använde disketter, vilket möjliggjorde större spel och inbyggd sparfunktion.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="zh_CN"><variables><systemDescription>任天堂于 1986 年发布的红白机外设，使用可读写磁碟，是《塞尔达传说》和《银河战士》的首发平台。</systemDescription></variables></language>
</theme>
