<theme>
    <variables>
        <systemName>FM Towns</systemName>
        <systemDescription>The FM Towns is a powerful Japanese personal computer built by Fujitsu from 1989 to 1997, known for being one of the first systems to standardize CD-ROM drives for gaming. It began as a proprietary multimedia-focused PC, featuring high-quality 2D graphics and CD-quality audio, which made it a premier platform for arcade ports and visual novels. In 1993, Fujitsu released the FM Towns Marty, the world's first 32-bit CD-based home console, fully compatible with the computer's vast library of games.</systemDescription>
        <systemManufacturer>Fujitsu</systemManufacturer>
        <systemReleaseYear>1989</systemReleaseYear>
        <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
        <systemColor>6d8efd</systemColor>
        <systemColorPalette1>9D9D9D</systemColorPalette1>
        <systemColorPalette2>009971</systemColorPalette2>
    </variables>
    <language name="es_ES">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>El FM Towns es un potente ordenador personal japonés fabricado por Fujitsu entre 1989 y 1997, destacado por ser uno de los primeros sistemas en estandarizar el uso de CD-ROM para videojuegos. Comenzó como un PC orientado al multimedia, ofreciendo gráficos 2D de alta calidad y audio de CD, lo que lo convirtió en la plataforma ideal para conversiones de arcade y novelas visuales. En 1993, Fujitsu lanzó la FM Towns Marty, la primera consola de 32 bits basada en CD del mundo, totalmente compatible con la extensa biblioteca del ordenador.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Ordenador</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="fr_FR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Le FM Towns est un puissant ordinateur personnel japonais construit par Fujitsu entre 1989 et 1997, célèbre pour avoir été l'un des premiers systèmes à généraliser le lecteur CD-ROM pour les jeux. Conçu à l'origine comme un PC multimédia, il offrait des graphismes 2D exceptionnels et un son de qualité CD, devenant une plateforme de choix pour les portages d'arcade. En 1993, Fujitsu a sorti la FM Towns Marty, la première console de salon 32 bits au monde basée sur le CD, entièrement compatible avec la logithèque de l'ordinateur.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Ordinateur</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="de_DE">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Der FM Towns ist ein leistungsstarker japanischer Personal Computer, der von 1989 bis 1997 von Fujitsu gebaut wurde und als eines der ersten Systeme CD-ROM-Laufwerke für Spiele standardisierte. Er begann als proprietärer, multimedia-orientierter PC mit hochwertiger 2D-Grafik und Audio in CD-Qualität, was ihn zu einer erstklassigen Plattform für Arcade-Portierungen machte. 1993 veröffentlichte Fujitsu mit dem FM Towns Marty die weltweit erste 32-Bit-CD-Heimkonsole, die vollständig mit der umfangreichen Spielebibliothek des Computers kompatibel war.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="it_IT">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>L'FM Towns è un potente personal computer giapponese costruito da Fujitsu dal 1989 al 1997, noto per essere stato uno dei primi sistemi a standardizzare l'uso del CD-ROM per il gaming. Nato come PC multimediale proprietario, offriva una grafica 2D di alta qualità e audio di qualità CD, diventando una piattaforma d'eccellenza per conversioni arcade e visual novel. Nel 1993, Fujitsu rilasciò l'FM Towns Marty, la prima console a 32 bit basata su CD al mondo, totalmente compatibile con la vasta libreria di giochi del computer.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="pt_BR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>O FM Towns é um poderoso computador pessoal japonês fabricado pela Fujitsu de 1989 a 1997, conhecido por ser um dos primeiros sistemas a padronizar o uso de CD-ROM para jogos. Começou como um PC proprietário focado em multimídia, apresentando gráficos 2D de alta qualidade e áudio de qualidade de CD, o que o tornou uma plataforma premium para ports de arcade. Em 1993, a Fujitsu lançou o FM Towns Marty, o primeiro console de 32 bits baseado em CD do mundo, totalmente compatível com a vasta biblioteca de jogos do computador.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Computador</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ja_JP">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>FMタウンズは、1989年から1997年にかけて富士通が製造した日本製のパーソナルコンピュータで、ゲーム用CD-ROMドライブを標準搭載した先駆け的システムとして知られています。マルチメディアに特化した独自のPCとして誕生し、高品質な2DグラフィックスとCD音源を実現したことで、アーケード移植作やビジュアルノベルの主要プラットフォームとなりました。1993年には、世界初の32ビットCD搭載型家庭用ゲーム機「FMタウンズマーティ」も発売され、コンピュータ版の膨大なゲームライブラリをそのまま楽しむことが可能でした。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>コンピューター</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
</theme>