<theme>
    <variables>
        <systemName>PC-88</systemName>
        <systemDescription>The PC-8800 series, commonly known as the PC-88, is a legendary line of 8-bit home computers released by NEC in 1981. Built around the Zilog Z80 processor, it became one of Japan's "Big Four" personal computers of the 1980s, dominating the market alongside the MSX and Sharp X1. The system is revered by gamers for its role in the birth of the JRPG and Visual Novel genres, boasting a massive library of titles from iconic developers like Nihon Falcom, Enix, and Square, all enhanced by its sophisticated FM synthesis sound capabilities.</systemDescription>
        <systemManufacturer>NEC</systemManufacturer>
        <systemReleaseYear>1981</systemReleaseYear>
        <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
        <systemColor>3C518B</systemColor>
        <systemColorPalette1>B6A781</systemColorPalette1>
        <systemColorPalette2>342B22</systemColorPalette2>
    </variables>

    <language name="es_ES">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>La serie PC-8800, conocida comúnmente como PC-88, es una legendaria línea de ordenadores domésticos de 8 bits lanzada por NEC en 1981. Basada en el procesador Zilog Z80, se convirtió en uno de los "Cuatro Grandes" ordenadores personales de Japón en los años 80, dominando el mercado junto al MSX y el Sharp X1. El sistema es venerado por los jugadores por su papel fundamental en el nacimiento de los géneros JRPG y Visual Novel, contando con una enorme biblioteca de títulos de desarrolladores icónicos como Nihon Falcom, Enix y Square.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Ordenador</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="fr_FR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>La série PC-8800, plus connue sous le nom de PC-88, est une gamme légendaire d'ordinateurs domestiques 8 bits lancée par NEC en 1981. Architecturée autour du processeur Zilog Z80, elle est devenue l'un des "quatre grands" ordinateurs personnels japonais des années 80. Le système est particulièrement respecté pour son rôle crucial dans la naissance des genres JRPG et Visual Novel, avec une ludothèque massive comprenant des titres de développeurs emblématiques tels que Nihon Falcom, Enix et Square.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Ordinateur</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="de_DE">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Die PC-8800-Serie, allgemein bekannt als PC-88, ist eine legendäre Reihe von 8-Bit-Heimcomputern, die 1981 von NEC veröffentlicht wurde. Basierend auf dem Zilog Z80-Prozessor wurde er zu einem der "Großen Vier" japanischen Computer der 1980er Jahre. Das System wird von Spielern für seine fundamentale Rolle bei der Entstehung der JRPG- und Visual Novel-Genres verehrt und verfügt über eine riesige Bibliothek von Titeln ikonischer Entwickler wie Nihon Falcom, Enix und Square, die oft durch seine fortschrittliche FM-Synthese-Soundhardware glänzten.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="it_IT">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>La serie PC-8800, comunemente nota come PC-88, è una leggendaria linea di home computer a 8 bit rilasciata da NEC nel 1981. Basata sul processore Zilog Z80, divenne uno dei "Grandi Quattro" personal computer giapponesi degli anni '80. Il sistema è venerato dai videogiocatori per il suo ruolo centrale nella nascita dei generi JRPG e Visual Novel, vantando una vasta libreria di titoli di sviluppatori iconici come Nihon Falcom, Enix e Square, supportati da eccellenti capacità sonore in sintesi FM.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="pt_BR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>A série PC-8800, comumente conhecida como PC-88, é uma lendária linha de computadores domésticos de 8 bits lançada pela NEC em 1981. Baseada no processador Zilog Z80, tornou-se um dos "Quatro Grandes" computadores pessoais do Japão na década de 1980. O sistema é venerado pelos jogadores por seu papel fundamental no nascimento dos gêneros JRPG e Visual Novel, possuindo uma enorme biblioteca de títulos de desenvolvedores icônicos como Nihon Falcom, Enix e Square.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Computador</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ja_JP">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>PC-8800シリーズ（通称PC-88）は、1981年にNECから発売された8ビットパソコンの金字塔です。Z80搭載のこのマシンは、MSXやX1と並び、80年代の日本における「マイコン御三家（または四大機種）」の一つとして市場を席巻しました。特にJRPGやビジュアルノベルというジャンルの確立において極めて重要な役割を果たし、日本ファルコム、エニックス、スクウェアといった名だたるメーカーが数々の名作を世に送り出したことで、今なおレトロゲームファンの間で神格化されています。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>コンピューター</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
</theme>