<theme>
    <variables>
        <systemName>WonderSwan</systemName>
        <systemDescription>The WonderSwan was a handheld console released in 1999 by Bandai. Designed by Gunpei Yokoi, it featured a unique vertical and horizontal layout, excellent battery life, and a library of exclusive anime-based titles and RPGs like Final Fantasy.</systemDescription>
        <systemManufacturer>Bandai</systemManufacturer>
        <systemReleaseYear>1999</systemReleaseYear>
        <systemHardwareType>Portable</systemHardwareType>
        <systemCoverSize>3-4</systemCoverSize>
        <systemCoverSizeType>portrait</systemCoverSizeType>
        <systemColor>eeeeee</systemColor>
        <systemColorPalette1>999999</systemColorPalette1>
        <systemColorPalette2>ffffff</systemColorPalette2>
        <systemColorPalette3>333333</systemColorPalette3>
        <systemColorPalette4>000000</systemColorPalette4>
        <systemCartSize>1-1</systemCartSize>
    </variables>
    <language name="ar_SA"><variables><systemDescription>جهاز محمول من بانداي، صممه غونبي يوكوي، تميز بإمكانية اللعب أفقياً وعمودياً.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="de_DE"><variables><systemDescription>Ein Handheld von Bandai, entworfen von Gunpei Yokoi, der sowohl horizontal als auch vertikal spielbar war.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="es_ES"><variables><systemDescription>Consola portátil de Bandai diseñada por Gunpei Yokoi. Podía jugarse tanto en vertical como en horizontal y tuvo grandes exclusivas de anime.</systemDescription><systemHardwareType>Portátil</systemHardwareType></variables></language>
    <language name="fr_FR"><variables><systemDescription>Console portable japonaise unique pouvant être tenue verticalement ou horizontalement.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="it_IT"><variables><systemDescription>Console portatile progettata da Gunpei Yokoi, famosa per il suo design versatile e i titoli Bandai.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="ja_JP"><variables><systemDescription>バンダイから発売された携帯機。横持ちと縦持ちの両方で遊べる独創的な設計が特徴です。</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="pl_PL"><variables><systemDescription>Przenośna konsola firmy Bandai, pozwalająca na grę w orientacji pionowej i poziomej.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="pt_BR"><variables><systemDescription>Portátil da Bandai projetado por Gunpei Yokoi, com um design único que permitia jogar em duas posições.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="ru_RU"><variables><systemDescription>Портативная система от Bandai, позволявшая играть как в горизонтальном, так и в вертикальном режиме.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="sv_SE"><variables><systemDescription>En bärbar konsol från Bandai som kunde användas både horisontellt och vertikalt.</systemDescription></variables></language>
    <language name="zh_CN"><variables><systemDescription>由横井军平设计的掌机，支持横向和纵向两种操作模式，拥有大量动漫IP游戏。</systemDescription></variables></language>
</theme>
