<theme>
    <variables>
        <systemName>Xbox One</systemName>
        <systemDescription>The Xbox One is an eighth-generation home video game console developed by Microsoft. Released in 2013 as the successor to the Xbox 360, it initially positioned itself as an "all-in-one" entertainment system. Over time, Microsoft shifted focus back to hardcore gaming, introducing the high-end Xbox One X and the successful Xbox Game Pass service. Notably, most of its library is shared with Windows, reflecting Microsoft's ecosystem-wide approach to gaming.</systemDescription>
        <systemManufacturer>Microsoft</systemManufacturer>
        <systemReleaseYear>2013</systemReleaseYear>
        <systemReleaseDate>2013-11-22</systemReleaseDate>
        <systemReleaseDateFormated>November 22, 2013</systemReleaseDateFormated>
        <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
        <systemCoverSize>243-340</systemCoverSize>
        <systemCoverSizeType>portrait</systemCoverSizeType>
        <systemColor>0099D7</systemColor>
        <systemColorPalette1>F5F8F8</systemColorPalette1>
        <systemColorPalette2>CECECE</systemColorPalette2>
        <systemColorPalette3>107C10</systemColorPalette3>
        <systemColorPalette4>7CB74E</systemColorPalette4>
        <systemCartSize>1-1</systemCartSize>
    </variables>

    <language name="ar_SA">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>جهاز Xbox One هو جهاز ألعاب فيديو منزلي من الجيل الثامن طورته شركة Microsoft. تم إصداره في عام 2013 كخليفة لجهاز Xbox 360، وركز في البداية على كونه نظام ترفيه متكامل. بمرور الوقت، أعادت الشركة التركيز على الألعاب، وأطلقت Xbox One X القوي وخدمة Xbox Game Pass الناجحة. من الملاحظ أن معظم مكتبة ألعابه متوفرة أيضاً على نظام Windows.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>وحدة التحكم</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="bs_BA">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Xbox One je Microsoftova konzola osme generacije, objavljena 2013. godine kao nasljednik Xboxa 360. Iako je u početku bila fokusirana na multimediju, kasnije se vratila fokusu na igre uz pomoć usluga poput Xbox Game Passa. Većina njenih naslova dostupna je i na Windows operativnom sistemu, što odražava Microsoftovu strategiju jedinstvenog ekosistema.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Konzola</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ca_ES">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>La Xbox One és una consola de vuitena generació desenvolupada per Microsoft. Llançada el 2013 com a successora de la Xbox 360, es va posicionar inicialment com un sistema d'entreteniment "tot en un". Amb el temps, Microsoft va tornar a centrar-se en el gaming pur, introduint la Xbox One X i el servei Xbox Game Pass. Molts dels seus jocs es comparteixen amb Windows.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="de_DE">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Die Xbox One ist eine von Microsoft entwickelte Heimvideospielkonsole der achten Generation. Sie wurde 2013 als Nachfolgerin der Xbox 360 veröffentlicht. Während sich das Marketing anfangs auf Multimedia-Funktionen konzentrierte, änderte sich dies mit der Einführung der Xbox One X und dem Game Pass. Bemerkenswert ist, dass Microsoft die meisten Spiele gleichzeitig für das Windows-Betriebssystem anbietet.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Konsole</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="es_ES">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>La Xbox One es una consola de octava generación desarrollada por Microsoft. Lanzada en 2013 como sucesora de la Xbox 360, inicialmente se posicionó como un sistema de entretenimiento integral. Con el tiempo, el enfoque volvió al gaming de alto rendimiento con la Xbox One X y el servicio Xbox Game Pass. La mayoría de sus juegos están disponibles también en el ecosistema Windows.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="fr_FR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>La Xbox One est une console de salon de huitième génération développée par Microsoft. Sortie en 2013 pour succéder à la Xbox 360, elle s'est d'abord présentée comme un système multimédia complet. Par la suite, Microsoft a recentré son discours sur le jeu avec la Xbox One X et le service Xbox Game Pass. La plupart de ses titres sont également disponibles sur PC via Windows.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="hr_HR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Xbox One je igraća konzola osme generacije koju je razvio Microsoft. Objavljena je 2013. kao nasljednik Xboxa 360. Iako je u početku reklamirana kao multimedijski sustav, kasnije se fokus vratio na igre, posebno uvođenjem Xbox One X konzole i Game Pass usluge. Većina igara dijeli se s Windows platformom.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Konzola</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="it_IT">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>La Xbox One è una console di ottava generazione sviluppata da Microsoft. Rilasciata nel 2013 come successore della Xbox 360, inizialmente puntava a essere un sistema di intrattenimento "tutto in uno". Nel corso degli anni, Microsoft ha riportato il focus sul gaming con la potente Xbox One X e il servizio Xbox Game Pass. La maggior parte della sua libreria è condivisa con Windows.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ja_JP">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Xbox Oneは、マイクロソフトが開発した第8世代の家庭用ゲーム機です。Xbox 360の後継機として2013年に発売されました。当初はマルチメディア機能を強調していましたが、後に強力なXbox One XやXbox Game Passサービスの導入により、ゲーム中心の戦略へと回帰しました。多くのタイトルがWindowsでも提供されており、マイクロソフトのエコシステムを象徴するハードウェアとなりました。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>コンソール</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ko_KR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Xbox One은 Microsoft에서 개발한 8세대 가정용 비디오 게임 콘솔입니다. 2013년 Xbox 360의 후속작으로 출시되었으며, 초기에는 올인원 엔터테인먼트 기기를 표방했으나 점차 Xbox Game Pass와 강력한 성능의 Xbox One X를 통해 게임 본연의 가치에 집중했습니다. 대부분의 게임이 Windows PC와 공유되는 것이 특징입니다.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>콘솔</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="nl_NL">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>De Xbox One is een achtste generatie spelcomputer ontwikkeld door Microsoft. Uitgebracht in 2013 als opvolger van de Xbox 360, werd hij aanvankelijk gepositioneerd als een multimedia-entertainmentsysteem. Later verschoof de focus weer naar gaming met de Xbox One X en Xbox Game Pass. De meeste spellen op deze console zijn ook beschikbaar op het Windows-platform.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="pl_PL">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Xbox One to konsola ósmej generacji opracowana przez Microsoft. Wydana w 2013 roku jako następca Xbox 360, początkowo promowana jako centrum multimedialne. Z czasem Microsoft powrócił do korzeni gamingowych, wprowadzając potężny model Xbox One X oraz usługę Xbox Game Pass. Większość gier z tej konsoli dostępna jest również na systemie Windows.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Konsola</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="pt_BR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>O Xbox One é um console de oitava geração desenvolvido pela Microsoft. Lançado em 2013 como sucessor do Xbox 360, inicialmente focou em ser um centro de entretenimento. Com o tempo, a Microsoft retomou o foco nos jogos com o potente Xbox One X e o serviço Xbox Game Pass. É notável que a maioria de sua biblioteca seja compartilhada com o sistema Windows.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Console</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="pt_PT">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>A Xbox One é uma consola de oitava geração desenvolvida pela Microsoft, lançada em 2013 como sucessora da Xbox 360. Embora inicialmente focada em multimédia, a estratégia mudou com o lançamento da Xbox One X e do serviço Xbox Game Pass. A grande maioria dos seus jogos está também disponível para Windows, integrando o ecossistema da Microsoft.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Consola</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ro_RO">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Xbox One este o consolă de jocuri video din a opta generație dezvoltată de Microsoft. Lansată în 2013 ca succesor al Xbox 360, s-a poziționat inițial ca un sistem multimedia. Ulterior, Microsoft a revenit la focusul pe gaming cu modelul Xbox One X și serviciul Xbox Game Pass. Majoritatea jocurilor sale sunt disponibile și pe sistemul de operare Windows.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Consolă</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ru_RU">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Xbox One — игровая приставка восьмого поколения от Microsoft, выпущенная в 2013 году. Изначально позиционировалась как универсальный медиацентр, но позже фокус сместился на гейминг с выходом Xbox One X и сервиса Xbox Game Pass. Большинство игр консоли также доступны на Windows, что является частью единой экосистемы Microsoft.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Консоль</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="sr_RS">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Xbox One је конзола осме генерације коју је развио Microsoft. Објављена је 2013. као наследник Xbox 360 система. Иако је првобитно замишљена као мултимедијални уређај, фокус се вратио на игре кроз Xbox One X и Game Pass услугу. Већина наслова је доступна и за Windows оперативни систем.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Конзола</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="sv_SE">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Xbox One är en åttonde generationens spelkonsol utvecklad av Microsoft. Den släpptes 2013 som efterföljare till Xbox 360. Efter en initial satsning på multimedia återgick fokus till renodlad gaming med Xbox One X och Xbox Game Pass. De flesta spel är även tillgängliga på Windows, vilket knyter samman Microsofts ekosystem.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Konsol</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="zh_CN">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Xbox One 是微软开发的第八代家用游戏机，于 2013 年作为 Xbox 360 的继任者发布。最初定位于全能娱乐系统，后来通过 Xbox One X 和 Xbox Game Pass 服务重新聚焦于核心游戏玩家。值得注意的是，其大部分游戏库与 Windows 共享，体现了微软的跨平台生态战略。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>控制台</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="zh_TW">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Xbox One 是微軟開發的第八代家用遊戲主機，於 2013 年作為 Xbox 360 的後繼機種推出。最初定位為全方位娛樂系統，隨後透過 Xbox One X 與 Xbox Game Pass 服務重新聚焦於遊戲本質。其大部分遊戲作品皆與 Windows 平台共享，展現了微軟整合生態系的策略。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>控制台</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
</theme>