<theme>
    <variables>
        <systemName>ZX81</systemName>
        <systemDescription>The ZX81 is a home computer that was produced by Sinclair Research and manufactured in Dundee, Scotland, by Timex Corporation. Launched in 1981 as the successor to the ZX80, it was designed to be a low-cost introduction to home computing. It was a massive success, selling over 1.5 million units. Known for its distinct black case and pressure-sensitive membrane keyboard, the ZX81 operated with just 1 KB of RAM and used audio cassettes for storage. It was the machine that truly brought computing to the British general public.</systemDescription>
        <systemManufacturer>Sinclair</systemManufacturer>
        <systemReleaseYear>1981</systemReleaseYear>
        <systemReleaseDate>1981-03-05</systemReleaseDate>
        <systemReleaseDateFormated>March 5, 1981</systemReleaseDateFormated>
        <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
        <systemColor>B92E34</systemColor>
        <systemColorPalette1>EF5857</systemColorPalette1>
        <systemColorPalette2>403E4B</systemColorPalette2>
        <systemColorPalette3>D2CECD</systemColorPalette3>
        <systemColorPalette4>191222</systemColorPalette4>
        <systemCartSize>1-1</systemCartSize>
    </variables>

    <language name="ar_SA">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>جهاز ZX81 هو كمبيوتر منزلي أنتجته شركة Sinclair Research وتم إطلاقه في عام 1981 كخليفة لجهاز ZX80. تم تصميمه ليكون مقدمة منخفضة التكلفة للحوسبة المنزلية وحقق نجاحاً هائلاً ببيع أكثر من 1.5 مليون وحدة. اشتهر الجهاز بلوحة مفاتيح غشائية حساسة للضغط وذاكرة RAM بسعة 1 كيلوبايت فقط. كان هو الجهاز الذي نقل الحوسبة إلى عامة الناس في بريطانيا.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>الحاسب الآلي</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="bs_BA">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>ZX81 je kućni računar koji je proizveo Sinclair Research 1981. godine kao nasljednika modela ZX80. Dizajniran je kao jeftin uvod u kućno računarstvo i postigao je ogroman uspjeh sa više od 1,5 miliona prodatih jedinica. Poznat po svojoj membranskoj tastaturi osjetljivoj na pritisak i memoriji od samo 1 KB RAM-a, ZX81 je bio uređaj koji je računarstvo približio široj javnosti.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Računar</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ca_ES">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>El ZX81 és un ordinador domèstic produït per Sinclair Research el 1981 com a successor del ZX80. Dissenyat per ser una introducció de baix cost a la informàtica domèstica, va tenir un gran èxit amb més d'1,5 milions d'unitats venudes. Conegut pel seu teclat de membrana i només 1 KB de RAM, va ser la màquina que realment va portar la informàtica al gran públic britànic.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="de_DE">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Der ZX81 ist ein Heimcomputer von Sinclair Research, der 1981 als Nachfolger des ZX80 erschien. Er war als preiswerter Einstieg in die Computerwelt gedacht und wurde mit über 1,5 Millionen verkauften Einheiten ein riesiger Erfolg. Bekannt für seine Folientastatur und lediglich 1 KB RAM, war der ZX81 das Gerät, das die Computertechnik in Großbritannien für die breite Masse zugänglich machte.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="es_ES">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>El ZX81 es un ordenador doméstico producido por Sinclair Research en 1981 como sucesor del ZX80. Diseñado como una introducción de bajo coste a la informática, vendió más de 1,5 millones de unidades. Famoso por su teclado de membrana y su escasa memoria de 1 KB de RAM, fue el sistema que realmente democratizó la informática en el Reino Unido, permitiendo que el público general tuviera su primer contacto con la programación.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Ordenador</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="fr_FR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Le ZX81 est un ordinateur familial produit par Sinclair Research en 1981. Successeur du ZX80, il a été conçu pour démocratiser l'informatique grâce à son prix réduit. Vendu à plus d'1,5 million d'exemplaires, il est célèbre pour son clavier à membrane et sa mémoire de seulement 1 Ko. C'est la machine qui a véritablement lancé la micro-informatique grand public au Royaume-Uni.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Ordinateur</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="hr_HR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>ZX81 je kućno računalo koje je Sinclair Research proizveo 1981. godine. Dizajniran kao jeftin ulaz u svijet računalstva, prodan je u više od 1,5 milijuna primjeraka. Poznat po svojoj membranskoj tipkovnici i samo 1 KB RAM-a, ZX81 je bio ključni uređaj koji je računalstvo učinio dostupnim široj javnosti u Britaniji.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Računalo</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="it_IT">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>Lo ZX81 è un home computer prodotto da Sinclair Research nel 1981 come successore dello ZX80. Progettato come introduzione a basso costo all'informatica, vendette oltre 1,5 milioni di unità. Celebre per la sua tastiera a membrana e la memoria di solo 1 KB di RAM, fu il computer che portò la rivoluzione digitale nelle case del grande pubblico britannico.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ja_JP">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>ZX81は、1981年にシンクレア・リサーチから発売された低価格なホームコンピュータです。ZX80の後継機として、一般家庭にコンピュータを普及させるために設計され、150万台以上を売り上げる大ヒットとなりました。感圧式のメンブレンキーボードとわずか1KBのRAMが特徴で、英国においてコンピュータが一部の愛好家だけのものでなくなるきっかけを作った伝説的なマシンです。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>コンピューター</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ko_KR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>ZX81은 1981년 싱클레어 리서치에서 제작한 가정용 컴퓨터입니다. ZX80의 후속작으로, 저렴한 가격을 통해 일반 대중에게 컴퓨터를 보급하기 위해 설계되었습니다. 150만 대 이상 판매된 이 기기는 감압식 멤브레인 키보드와 1KB의 적은 메모리가 특징이며, 영국 가정용 컴퓨터 시장의 대중화를 이끈 선구적인 모델입니다.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>컴퓨터</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="nl_NL">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>De ZX81 is een thuiscomputer van Sinclair Research uit 1981. Als opvolger van de ZX80 was hij bedoeld als een betaalbare kennismaking met computers. Met meer dan 1,5 miljoen verkochte exemplaren was het een enorm succes. Bekend om zijn membraantoetsenbord en slechts 1 KB RAM, was dit de machine die computergebruik in Groot-Brittannië voor het grote publiek toegankelijk maakte.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="pl_PL">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>ZX81 to komputer domowy firmy Sinclair Research wprowadzony na rynek w 1981 roku. Zaprojektowany jako tani wstęp do informatyki, sprzedał się w liczbie ponad 1,5 miliona egzemplarzy. Charakterystyczna klawiatura membranowa i zaledwie 1 KB pamięci RAM to jego znaki rozpoznawcze. Była to maszyna, która zrewolucjonizowała dostęp do komputerów w brytyjskich domach.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Komputer</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="pt_BR">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>O ZX81 é um computador doméstico produzido pela Sinclair Research em 1981 como sucessor do ZX80. Projetado para ser uma introdução de baixo custo à computação, vendeu mais de 1,5 milhão de unidades. Famoso pelo teclado de membrana e apenas 1 KB de RAM, foi o sistema que realmente democratizou a informática no Reino Unido e serviu de base para diversos clones ao redor do mundo.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Computador</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="pt_PT">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>O ZX81 é um computador doméstico da Sinclair Research, lançado em 1981 como sucessor do ZX80. Foi desenhado para ser uma introdução económica à informática doméstica e tornou-se um enorme sucesso com mais de 1,5 milhões de unidades vendidas. Com o seu teclado de membrana e apenas 1 KB de RAM, foi a máquina que levou a computação ao grande público britânico.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Computador</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ro_RO">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>ZX81 este un computer de casă produs de Sinclair Research în 1981, succesor al modelului ZX80. Creat ca o introducere accesibilă în lumea informaticii, s-a vândut în peste 1,5 milioane de unități. Cunoscut pentru tastatura sa cu membrană și memoria de doar 1 KB RAM, acesta a fost dispozitivul care a democratizat accesul la calculatoare în Marea Britanie.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Computer</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="ru_RU">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>ZX81 — домашний компьютер, выпущенный компанией Sinclair Research в 1981 году как преемник ZX80. Задуманный как доступное введение в мир программирования, он разошелся тиражом более 1,5 миллиона штук. Известный своей мембранной клавиатурой и памятью всего в 1 КБ, ZX81 стал устройством, которое сделало компьютеры по-настоящему массовыми в Великобритании.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Компьютер</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="sr_RS">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>ZX81 је кућни рачунар који је Sinclair Research представио 1981. године. Дизајниран као јефтин увод у свет рачунара, продат је у преко 1,5 милиона примерака. Познат по својој мембранској тастатури и свега 1 KB RAM-а, ZX81 је био кључни систем који је приближио рачунарство широким народним масама у Британији.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Рачунар</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="sv_SE">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>ZX81 är en hemdator från Sinclair Research som lanserades 1981 som efterföljare till ZX80. Den var tänkt som en billig introduktion till datorvärlden och blev en stor succé med över 1,5 miljoner sålda enheter. Med sitt membrantangentbord och endast 1 KB RAM var det maskinen som verkligen gjorde datorer tillgängliga för den brittiska allmänheten.</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>Dator</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="zh_CN">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>ZX81 是 Sinclair Research 于 1981 年推出的家用电脑，是 ZX80 的继任者。它的设计初衷是让大众能以低廉的价格接触电脑，最终销量超过 150 万台。它以薄膜键盘和仅 1 KB 的内存而闻名，是真正让计算机走进英国普通家庭的里程碑式产品。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>计算机</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
    <language name="zh_TW">
        <variables>
            <systemDescription>ZX81 是 Sinclair Research 於 1981 年推出的家用電腦，為 ZX80 的後繼機種。其設計旨在以低廉成本讓大眾接觸電腦，最終創下超過 150 萬台的銷量。以其獨特的薄膜鍵盤和僅 1 KB RAM 記憶體著稱，是讓計算機技術在英國真正普及化的關鍵機器。</systemDescription>
            <systemHardwareType>電腦</systemHardwareType>
        </variables>
    </language>
</theme>